<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><testsuite xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://maven.apache.org/surefire/maven-surefire-plugin/xsd/surefire-test-report.xsd" name="https://www.example.com" tests="7" failures="7" errors="0" skipped="0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><properties><property name="name" value="https://www.example.com"/><property name="host" value="www.example.com"/><property name="port" value="443"/><property name="ssl" value="true"/><property name="version" value="2.10.0"/><property name="generated" value="Sat, 27 Feb 2021 02:47:36"/></properties><testcase time="" name="Strict-Transport-Security Header Not Set"><failure type="Low (High)" message="&lt;p&gt;HTTP Strict Transport Security (HSTS) is a web security policy mechanism whereby a web server declares that complying user agents (such as a web browser) are to interact with it using only secure HTTPS connections (i.e. HTTP layered over TLS/SSL). HSTS is an IETF standards track protocol and is specified in RFC 6797.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="X-Content-Type-Options Header Missing"><failure type="Low (Medium)" message="&lt;p&gt;The Anti-MIME-Sniffing header X-Content-Type-Options was not set to 'nosniff'. This allows older versions of Internet Explorer and Chrome to perform MIME-sniffing on the response body, potentially causing the response body to be interpreted and displayed as a content type other than the declared content type. Current (early 2014) and legacy versions of Firefox will use the declared content type (if one is set), rather than performing MIME-sniffing.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="Server Leaks Version Information via &quot;Server&quot; HTTP Response Header Field"><failure type="Low (High)" message="&lt;p&gt;The web/application server is leaking version information via the &quot;Server&quot; HTTP response header. Access to such information may facilitate attackers identifying other vulnerabilities your web/application server is subject to.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="Retrieved from Cache"><failure type="Informational (Medium)" message="&lt;p&gt;The content was retrieved from a shared cache. If the response data is sensitive, personal or user-specific, this may result in sensitive information being leaked. In some cases, this may even result in a user gaining complete control of the session of another user, depending on the configuration of the caching components in use in their environment. This is primarily an issue where caching servers such as &quot;proxy&quot; caches are configured on the local network. This configuration is typically found in corporate or educational environments, for instance. &lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="Content Security Policy (CSP) Header Not Set"><failure type="Medium (High)" message="&lt;p&gt;Content Security Policy (CSP) is an added layer of security that helps to detect and mitigate certain types of attacks, including Cross Site Scripting (XSS) and data injection attacks. These attacks are used for everything from data theft to site defacement or distribution of malware. CSP provides a set of standard HTTP headers that allow website owners to declare approved sources of content that browsers should be allowed to load on that page — covered types are JavaScript, CSS, HTML frames, fonts, images and embeddable objects such as Java applets, ActiveX, audio and video files.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="X-Frame-Options Header Not Set"><failure type="Medium (Medium)" message="&lt;p&gt;X-Frame-Options header is not included in the HTTP response to protect against 'ClickJacking' attacks.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase><testcase time="" name="Incomplete or No Cache-control and Pragma HTTP Header Set"><failure type="Low (Medium)" message="&lt;p&gt;The cache-control and pragma HTTP header have not been set properly or are missing allowing the browser and proxies to cache content.&lt;/p&gt;"/></testcase></testsuite>